What was that?
Nothing.
Okay, just give me one little hint.
No, no hints.
We're almost there.
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
No, no, no.
Hey, you said you like surprises.
Yeah, I do.
When I know what they are.
You're going to love it.
Promise.
Oh, yeah.
I already love the view.
Ha ha.
Hello.
All right, here we are.
Watch your step, watch your step.
I can't see.
Ready?
Forward, stop.
I'm taking it off.
Now.
Are you kidding?
How?
I didn't even know this place was open
yet.
Pulled some favors and got us on the
list for opening night.
Oh!
You look really ugly.
Wow, uh...
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
You look like a million bucks.
Come on.
Hey!
Don't steal coins from the fountain.
It's bad luck.
Sorry sir.
Go on.
Smile.
Hello, sir.
Would you like a photo?
Thank you.
Watch your step, everyone.
You coming?
Uh, we'll...
take the next one.
Aw, come on.
We can fit you in.
Thanks.
Going up.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry, it does that sometimes.
Ah!
Some fun facts about the Scadvey Tower.
It's 494 feet tall and weighs over 9
,000 tons.
It's made of steel and
reinforced concrete and
glass.
And even more impressive,
the entire project was
completed five months ahead of schedule.
Is that a good thing?
What'd I tell you?
Nancy?
Yes?
May I help you?
We have a reservation.
Campbell.
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're
already over capacity
for opening night.
We cannot accommodate you.
If you wouldn't mind just stepping aside.
Thank you so much.
It's okay.
I worked it out with Jake.
Is he here?
I could speak...
We let Jake go this morning.
Thank you so much.
What's going on?
One second.
Sir, you're a very important man.
Maybe you could help me out.
Excuse me.
Please.
You're tearing me apart.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
If you wouldn't mind.
Oh, Mr. Fuller, how nice to see you.
We have a lovely table for you.
Thank you.
Let's go to the bar.
What?
Act natural.
Look at the view.
What?
I don't know.
You're scared of heights?
No, I'm just...
I've just never been this high up before.
I'm so sorry.
This night's turning into such a disaster.
I really wanted it to be perfect.
Hey.
It is perfect.
Because I'm with you.
Ah.
You okay?
I think I'll live.
Yeah?
Hey, look, free champagne.
That's my favorite kind.
Want me to ride up?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, where's the ladies' room?
Other side of the dance floor.
And I tumbled from the sky I got
to feeling I'm a-falling Loving you's the
reason why The reason
why You're the reason why Thank you.
We'll be right back.
Hi, sweetie.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine, thank you.
How far along are you?
What?
Oh, no, I'm not.
I don't know exactly.
Maybe one or two months.
That's wonderful news.
Isn't it?
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
Does he love you?
Yes.
Then he won't let go.
Thank you.
Of course.
Bye.
Okay, it's almost over.
Oh.
Hey, what?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I think so.
Come on.
Let's get some fresh air.
I really need to...
I'm sorry, I wanted to...
You go first.
Okay.
I was going to do this at dinner,
but seeing as we have this view...
Hey, don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Of course.
Fat ass.
Um...
These past few years have
been absolutely magical.
And that's, uh...
That's because of you.
Iris, I want to spend the rest of
my life with you.
You mean...
With us?
What?
Sorry.
I...
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
What?
You're not upset?
Are you kidding me?
No, this is...
This is incredible.
Really?
We're going to start a family.
Um, so...
Will you?
Oh, yes.
Is it too tight?
It's perfect.
Hey, let's go celebrate.
Shut up!
That has to mean my eyes will...
Children first!
To the
elevator!
Move!
Oh no.
Help.
Oh, I'll be right there.
Aghhhh!
Help me!
Well, I realize vector
multiplication is scary, but
it's not that scary.
Alright, that's it for today.
We'll start prepping
for the final next week.
Ms. Reyes, we need to talk.
We're a family, aren't we?
Don't throw that penny out of the air.
It could kill someone.
Everyone's gonna die!
This dream is ruining my life.
Mine too.
Every night, Steph.
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
I'm sorry.
Um, can I tell you something?
Yeah, what's up?
So, the woman in my dream, her name
is Iris, right?
Okay.
That was my grandmother's name.
I, uh, I think I'm dreaming about her.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
The thing is, I never even met her.
I don't even know if she's alive.
Okay, well, either go home and find out
about Grandma and
hope that stops the dreams,
or stay here and die in your sleep,
for real.
Because I will murder you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Love you!
Love you too.
Go home.
Yeah.
Quietly.
Steph.
Hey, there she is.
Hey, Dad.
Welcome home, sweetie.
So glad you're here.
Yeah, me too.
I miss you so much.
I know.
So great to see you.
Thank you, thank you.
Take that for you.
Hey, sorry.
Charlie took your room a while ago, and
my files are in his room, so I
made up the pull-out for you.
Is that okay?
Yeah, yeah, no, that sounds totally fine.
Hey, do we still have that box of
Mom's old stuff?
It had some photos, like an address book,
phone numbers in it.
Why do you want that?
It's not a big deal.
I just thought I saw it lying around
here somewhere.
Stephanie, what's going on?
Okay, this is going to sound really, really
weird, but I just need to find Mom's
mom, Iris.
Uh...
Okay, yeah, that is weird.
And you know, I got rid of those
boxes years ago, after Mom left.
Oh, hi, Charlie.
Hey.
Um, hi, Steph.
How are you?
It's so nice to see you.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, you going to the Cousins?
Whoa, now?
Hook, your sister, just got home.
I thought we could...
Actually, you know what?
I can drive you.
I was wanting to see them anyways.
It's fine.
Hey, if you're going to see your cousins,
please don't talk about
Iris to Uncle Howard.
Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
All right.
Bye, love you.
Love you, too.
Charlie?
Charlie, can you just
take these out, please?
I'm trying to talk to you.
What's your problem?
What?
I just...
You haven't said anything this entire time.
Well...
Steph, why are you here?
I mean, you only come home for holidays.
Okay, I have to tell you something, but
you have to promise not to tell Dad.
Are you pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
I don't know.
Why would you even...
That's not...
I mean, you're in college.
Can you just promise me you won't tell
Dad?
Why would I tell Dad?
It's serious, Charlie.
All right.
Okay.
I am on academic probation.
Whoa.
Stop laughing.
If I don't get my grades up...
This is kind of a big moment for
me.
This is kind of funny.
Straight A's.
You're a class president.
Miss Valedictorian.
Charlie, it's not funny.
If I don't get my grades up, I
will lose my scholarship.
Oh.
I buzzed.
Sorry.
What happened?
I can't sleep.
Every time I close my eyes, I have
this same recurring nightmare
about Iris, our grandmother.
I don't...
I mean, it has to mean something.
I don't know.
I dream weird things.
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last
night.
What?
Like, the hot dog was eating me.
Okay.
Dude, can you just do something?
Dude, calm down.
Just move a little bit.
I can't pause over these online messages.
I have to look under these.
Can you do me a kindness?
Fuck off.
Do you remember what happened last time?
It's a ranked match.
What's going on?
I can't find Paco.
Dude, again?
Who's Paco?
No way.
Hey, hey, cuz.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, can you help us look?
And just watch your
feet when you're stepping.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I just...
I gotta talk to your dad first.
The fuck are you doing home?
Oh, dude, she's fucking out of school.
Hey.
Welcome to the club.
Eric, dude, have you looked anywhere?
Paco's not upstairs.
Oh, but look who's down here.
Hi, Julia.
Oh my gosh.
How you been?
Charlie.
Jules.
There's my little Romeo.
So, wait, how did the promposal with Jenny
go?
Dude, she said yes.
Oh my God.
Stop.
Okay, wait.
Who's, uh, who's Jenny?
Oh, he met her in Junior Lifeguards.
Junior Lifeguards.
Charlie, I didn't...
I didn't know you were
doing Junior Lifeguards.
Okay.
So what are you gonna wear?
Uh, just gonna keep it simple.
No black blazer.
Okay.
But...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But with, like, a fun bow.
I like it.
Stop!
Stephanie!
Oh my gosh.
Hi, honey.
Hi, I'm Brenda.
How long are you here for?
Uh, not long.
Uh, is, is Uncle Howard around?
Yeah, yeah, he's out back.
I'll get him.
Howard!
Stephanie's here.
Come in.
Great.
You look a little tired.
Is everything okay?
Oh.
Stephanie!
Look at you!
Come here, come here.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
Hey, are you hungry?
I was just gonna make some lunch.
Uh, no, actually.
Uh, I came here because I wanted to
talk to you about your mother, Iris.
I know you don't like to talk about
her.
There's not much to tell.
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
It's just that I've been, I've been having
this recurring nightmare about her.
Oh, honey, it's probably just stress.
You should try melatonin.
Okay, but the weird thing is, I've been
dreaming about a real place from, from 50
years ago.
It was, like, a restaurant
called The Skyview.
You know what it is?
Did, did Iris tell you about it?
Uh, what did, what did she say?
Did, did she say anything?
Um, maybe, maybe if I could talk to
her...
Talk to who?
Uh, Steph is dreaming about Grandma Iris.
Psycho granny?
I thought she was dead.
Well, she's dead to us.
Stephie, Iris Campbell
is a very deeply disturbed
woman.
End of story.
Look, if I could just talk to her,
then, then maybe, maybe I can get these
dreams to stop.
Steph, just drop it.
I don't get it.
What, what happened that was so bad?
For one thing, she's the reason that your
mother's so screwed up.
What?
Look, I just don't want to talk about
this anymore, okay?
Uncle Howard, please, I just need to know.
Look, Stephie, after
our father died, Iris just
snapped.
She, she wouldn't let us go to school.
She locked us inside the house.
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we
could die.
And eventually it got so bad, I mean
so bad, that the state came in and
they took your mother and I away from
her.
But it didn't end there.
She, she tracked us
all through foster care.
And when the kids were born, she started
sending us these horrible
letters that were full
of obituaries and these
disturbing pictures of dead
bodies.
We had to move, so she couldn't contact
us anymore.
So, uh, do you still have any of
those letters, though?
I...
Stephie, listen to me.
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
And for your well-being and your safety,
stay the hell away from her.
I believe you.
I found Paco.
Thank God.
I'm sure he'd love to be in the
living room right now.
No way.
Come on, guys, let's go.
How did he even get in there?
I need you to help me.
You heard your uncle.
Just let it go.
You don't understand.
My whole life is falling apart because of
this dream.
And not only that, I feel like, I
feel like I'm losing my mind.
Please, you are the only person who can
help me.
Howard would never forgive me if I put
you in touch with Iris.
Please.
Whatever you do, do not look in the
bottom drawer of the dining room cabinet.
Hi, um, I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
Did you not see the signs?
Uh, uh, yeah, yes, I did, but...
Then get the fuck out of here.
No visitors.
I'm your granddaughter.
Stephanie.
Empty your pockets.
Phone, keys, everything.
Well, I'm not dangerous.
It's not you I'm afraid of.
Uh...
Come in slowly.
Shut the door.
Quick, quick, quick.
Don't move.
Oh, my God.
It really is you.
I can see your mother in you.
Hi, I'm Stephanie.
Stop, stop, don't.
Move.
Not until I tell you.
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
Getting me to let my guard down.
I...
Sit.
Okay, um, sit.
That's it.
So, how is Darlene?
Your mom, okay?
Oh, uh, no, I don't know.
She, uh, she left when I was ten,
so we don't see her anymore.
Oh.
But you saw my letters, that's why you're
here, right?
No.
Um, I'm actually here
because I've been dreaming
about the sky view.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, every single night for the past two
months, it's the same dream.
In it, you're on a date, but then
the dance floor breaks, and then there's an
explosion, and then you...
Fall and die.
Yeah.
Yeah, everyone dies.
It wasn't just your dream.
It was my premonition.
Years ago, at the sky view, I got
a glimpse into the future and saw what
death was about to do.
I was gonna do this at dinner, but
seeing as we have this view...
Hey, don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry, of course.
These past two years have
been absolutely magical,
and that's all because of you.
No, no, no, no, I...
This isn't right, I...
Is that a no?
Everyone's going to die.
The whole building is going to come down
and...
Are you serious?
The penny.
Iris?
Give me that.
What the hell, lady?
Give it to me!
What are you doing?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Iris?
Don't play!
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
The glass is about to break!
Everyone needs to get off now!
Wait, no!
Get off the dance floor!
Iris!
You need to get off!
Get off!
I saved a lot of lives that night.
Lives that were never meant to be saved.
They closed the restaurant after that.
Said it needed additional renovations.
But it never reopened.
Eventually they tore it down.
Wait, so you stopped the disaster?
Yes.
But death doesn't like it when you fuck
with his plans.
So over the years he came back.
And he killed everyone who was there that
night.
Including my Paul.
Wait, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Did you...
Did you say death came back?
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
Won't stop till he finishes the job.
But I taught myself how to see him
coming.
To anticipate his every move.
Been keeping him at bay for years now.
And now he's got me.
Cancer.
Believe that shit?
Sorry.
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
Wait, that's when I
started having my dream.
See?
It's a sign.
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what
you saw?
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition on to
you.
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor.
Who the hell knows?
What matters is that
when the universe speaks
you pay attention.
I see you, you fuck.
Um...
Who...
who are you talking to?
Death.
He thinks I'm distracted
because you're here.
I have to teach you everything in this
book.
It'll take some time to learn the basics.
So you'll need to stay here.
Stay here?
The outside world is too dangerous.
I haven't stepped out there in 20 years.
In here, we can be safe.
Oh.
See that?
Yeah.
This is all my research.
My life's work.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I...
I can't...
I can't stay here.
I...
I have to get back to school.
But, you know, I'll...
I'll come back and I'll visit.
No!
I'm sick!
I won't be alive that long.
You can't leave.
Don't you see?
Death is coming for our family.
Uh...
You don't believe me?
No, I...
I'm...
I think...
I think I made a mistake.
I think it...
I think it was probably just...
a dream.
No, wait!
At least take the book!
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come here.
This book is a lifeline.
It will show you everything you need to
know to keep our family safe.
You still don't believe me?
Step back.
What?
Why?
Seeing is believing.
No!
Hey, Steph.
Her face really exploded right in front of
you.
Is that like...
I'm...
Just leave her alone.
It's my bad, Steph.
I'm just curious.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
Yeah.
I'm sorry Uncle helped.
You were right about Iris.
I never...
I never should have went there.
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
I'm so sorry you had to go through
that.
She said something to me before she died.
She said death was coming for our family.
That's...
That's crazy, right?
Oh my God.
I can't believe it.
I emailed her.
I just didn't think she'd show up.
Come on.
You know what?
Um...
Demo?
Yeah.
Darlene!
Wow.
Um...
I can come back.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Come on.
Get down here.
Come here.
Think she'll come to the barbecue?
Steph, hey.
If she's going to Uncle
Howard's house, then
I'm not.
You can get a ride with Dad.
You're not even going to talk to her?
Come on.
You don't remember her like I do.
Just give her a chance.
Why?
Charlie, she abandoned us and now she rolls
in here?
After all these years and wants to act
like nothing happened?
Because he would do that.
Right?
Wait, what?
Nothing.
No.
What's that supposed to mean?
I tried calling you so many times.
And nothing.
Same with Julia.
You used to be best friends.
You don't even talk anymore.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry.
I...
I've just been distracted
the last couple of
months because of this nightmare.
What about before that?
It's been like this ever since you left.
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been
around either.
I'm not like her.
Okay?
I'm not crazy.
Yeah, you're right.
You're not crazy.
You just don't care.
All right.
Now you got it.
Watch out for splinters.
Hey, there she is.
Hey.
Come here.
I'm so glad you made it.
You know, I didn't think you were actually
going to come.
Thank you for inviting me.
Of course.
Come on in.
Hey, everybody.
Come on.
Come on over.
I made cookies.
That's great.
Can I try one?
Yes, of course.
Does this have peanut butter?
Yeah.
Are you trying to kill my brother?
Oh, my God.
Bobby's allergic.
Yeah.
I totally forgot.
I'm so sorry.
The important thing is that you're here.
So, uh, Bobby Bartender.
Drinks.
Drinks all around.
Family.
You don't get to pick the one you
get.
You just got to love the one that
you got.
Now, uh, our mother, she lived alone until
the day that she died.
And her death should be a reminder to
all of us to enjoy life and spend
the time that we have together.
Because we're not going to get any back.
I love you guys.
Aww.
Cheers to that.
Cheers.
Mmm.
This is strong.
What did you put in there?
Julia?
Oh, cool.
Are you all right?
Oh, my God.
There's a bug in there.
Your royalty.
Ah.
You are?
Actually, yeah.
I'm turning in my crowning job.
That's great.
Yeah.
Charlie!
Get up here!
Whoa!
Eric.
Ma.
Grill's ready.
Mind if I join you?
Have a seat.
Take the load off.
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
It's great, the setup you've got here.
Well, I wanted the kids to have a
happy childhood.
Unlike some people I know.
You're not talking about us, are you?
Oh, no.
We had a great childhood.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, look at me.
I turned out fabulous.
Yep.
Oh.
Howard.
What?
Come on.
What is that?
It looks like a house key.
I mean...
Come on.
You know we got the spare room.
And it's got to be better than bouncing
around trailer parks.
I don't think this is a good idea.
It's never too late for a second chance.
I'm sorry.
They're better off without me.
Pick up.
Pick up, come on.
You're onto me, right?
You're onto me.
Come show us your back
flip.
What?
No, no, no.
Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard.
Come on, Howard.
Howard.
Up him up.
There you go.
All right.
Here we go.
Watch out.
Wait.
Stop.
Oh.
Nice catch, Auntie.
All right.
Here we go.
Okay, Dad.
Let's do it.
Stay away from that edge.
Come on, Uncle Howard.
Here we go.
Just like college.
That was nice.
Careful, Howard.
I better get it out of there.
Hey, Stephanie.
You made it.
Stephanie.
I'm glad you decided to come.
Now the whole family's here.
Yeah.
I'm okay.
I'm all right.
Oh, good.
I'm okay.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Oh, God!
The former things are passed away.
Neither shall there be
mourning nor pain, and
he shall wipe away every tear from their
eyes, and death shall be no more.
Hey.
Where's all this stuff?
I found these papers in Iris' book.
They are obituaries
and articles for the people
who were at the Skyview on the night
that Iris had her premonition.
Each one of these people went on to
die in some weird and messed up way,
and not only that, they all died in
the same order as Iris' premonition.
Hundreds of people
were supposed to die that
night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
So death came back for them one by
one.
Since there were so many survivors, it took
years for death to get to all of
them, but eventually it got to Iris.
She was the last to die in the
premonition.
It was her and a little boy, but
she was prepared.
She single-handedly
held off death for decades.
Stephanie, sweetie,
I don't think this is the
appropriate time for this.
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has
anything to do with us, right?
Why are we even here?
No, that's it.
It has everything to do with us.
I mean, because death took so long to
make its way through
the survivors, these people
went on to have
families, families that they
never should have had.
So death took them too.
Don't you see this?
Death is coming for us because we were
never supposed to exist.
Okay, so why everybody in this room is
on death's hit list?
Bobby, Stock, that's what she's saying.
No, no, no.
Dad and Aunt Brenda
are safe because they're
not part of Iris' bloodline.
Okay, following the
pattern, death makes its way
down each branch by age.
So because Uncle
Howard was the oldest, it'll
start with his family
first, meaning Eric, you're
next.
Go fuck yourself.
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
Then it'll come for our
branch, starting with
Darlene, then me, then Charlie.
Charlie, you buying this?
I don't know.
This is so messed up.
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into
some kind of fucked-up conspiracy theory.
What is wrong with you?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not, it's not a conspiracy theory.
Fab, enough.
We're all gonna die.
Stop.
I can't listen to this for one more
minute.
That crazy woman's nonsense
has caused enough pain
and suffering for this family.
Hang on.
Aunt Brenda, please, just listen.
Leave me alone.
Okay, in Iris' book, she
mentions somebody who
cheated death and survived.
Stephanie.
Come on.
Eric, no, wait.
I'm worried about you.
Stop it.
Let me take care of this.
Come on, Bobby.
Brenda.
Let's go.
No, no, no, you can't.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Please.
You believe me, right?
I'm sorry.
Julian, look, I love you.
But sometimes I really hate you.
I know how convincing all of this can
be.
But it's not real.
How can you say that?
I know Iris taught you all of this.
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your life
the same way they did mine.
Thank you so much for that advice, but
I really don't need a mom anymore.
Wide open, wide.
All right, good.
Just gonna pinch, all right?
You ready?
Five, four, three.
Two.
Good job.
You're gonna hit the club.
I need you to lock up.
And don't touch any of my liquor.
No, no, you didn't say
anything about locking
up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You didn't say shit about closing, dude.
Yeah, cry me a river.
I hope you burn in hell.
You believe that shit?
My old man just died.
I come in as a favorite of that
asshole, and now he wants me to lock
up.
You know what that is?
Mm-hmm.
It's inconsiderate.
Anyway, you're all done.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Of course, hey, five-star review, yeah?
Like and subscribe and all the things.
No, I can't forget this
evening Or your face as you were leaving
But I guess that's just the way the
story goes And now it's only fair That
I should let you know You should forget
this evening Or your face as you were
leaving Oh,
goddammit.
Or your sorrow Yes, it should hold you
Ow.
Ow, ow.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Ow.
Come on.
No.
Okay.
Ow!
Shit!
Charlie, wake up.
Charlie, wake...
Charlie, wake up!
I've been trying to call Eric all night.
He's not answering me.
I don't know where he is.
I'm worried.
I'm sure he's fine.
Well, have you heard from him?
I'm going over there.
I need to check on him.
You're coming too, Charlie.
He's going to voicemail.
Is that him?
My friend just said
the tattoo parlor burned
down last night.
What?
Steph!
Ow!
Oh, what?
You're trying to kill me?
Eric?
Uh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
Dude!
We heard about the fire.
We thought you were dead.
I'm fine.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
I was so worried about you.
Yeah, a firefighter said I was lucky as
fuck that I was wearing
that leather jacket.
It barely got burned.
I'm wearing my favorite jacket, though.
What is this?
Oh, yeah, check it out.
I got branded.
Sick, right?
You like it?
You said you were asleep.
No, you were blowing up my phone like
a goddamn stalker.
What'd you want me to do?
Yeah, I don't get it.
You should be dead.
Right, yeah, yeah.
Or, you know, maybe...
Maybe death's not actually
coming for our family.
Because that would be fucking crazy.
Jesus shit!
Or maybe I'm invincible.
Eric?
Eric!
Yeah?
Eric, wait.
Stop.
Just wait, okay?
Just because death
didn't kill you last night
doesn't mean that you're safe.
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
Ooh.
Gonna move on its own, Steph?
Is that what it's gonna do?
It could fall.
And stay away from these kids.
I'll take my chances.
Steph, how is a couple kids with a
soccer ball gonna kill him?
I mean, I don't know.
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf
blower guy, which causes him to blow stuff
into the kid's eyes and then kick the
ball into his face.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Soccer ball into my face?
That does sound deadly.
I should be more careful.
Hey.
What's up?
What happened to you?
Charbroiled by death, apparently.
She came.
That was really bad.
Oh, wait.
Let me see that.
Eric, just stay away from the truck.
Oh, what?
This truck?
Stop.
Oh, my God.
Please.
This truck right here?
But it's such a beautiful truck.
Stop.
Don't touch it.
Eric, get away.
Stop.
You like that?
Can you just...
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Oh, Eric's tempted death again.
What's gonna happen?
What?
Stop doing that.
What's gonna happen?
Nothing at all.
How about that?
Look, I'm just trying to help you, okay?
Try less.
Yeah.
Honestly, we're so done with your garbage.
Can you please...
For the 1,500th time, no one gives
a shit about your
stupid little death curse,
okay?
So take a hint and leave us alone
because death's not coming for our family.
Julia!
What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger Stand
a little taller Doesn't
mean I'm lonely when
I'm alone What doesn't kill you makes a
fighter Put the fever high Julia!
No!
Give me your hand!
I got you!
Don't worry, you're not next!
Whoa, whoa!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
My sister's in the back!
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
We should have believed you, Steph.
No, I...
I screwed up the order and now Julia's
dead.
It's my fault.
Guys, look.
What happened was
traumatic and awful, but it's
not anybody's fault.
It's my fault.
Mom, it's not your fault.
It is my fault.
Stephanie, you were
only wrong about the order
because there was
something you didn't know.
Eric isn't Howard's biological son.
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
And Stephanie, I didn't believe you, so I
didn't say anything to you, and now my
little girl's dead.
Well, I don't understand.
Were you having an affair?
Your father and I were having such a
hard time, but it was good because I
got you.
I got you out of it.
Who's been a real dad, then?
Who's been a real dad?
It doesn't matter because
Howard loved you so,
so much.
Who is it?
Who?
Who's been a real dad?
Jerry Fenbury.
Oh, Jerry Fenbury?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no.
Jerry fucking Fenbury?
You don't know what we've gone through.
Oh, God.
What, is this why you always wanted to
play catch?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
All right, so that means that if it's
going in the right order, that I'm next,
right?
You gotta help me, Steph.
Mommy, I don't think that I can.
I mean, I thought I did, but I
don't...
No, but you can.
I mean, you predicted
exactly what was gonna
happen.
You just got the order wrong because you
didn't have all the information, Charlie.
What do you mean, predicted?
She saw everything.
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball.
Like, it was like there were pieces to
a puzzle and she just had to put
them together, you know what I mean?
Is that true?
Darlene, please, do not encourage this.
Marty, I mean...
I mean, it's everything in Iris' book.
It's like an equation.
It's math.
Stephanie, if you can see how all of
this fits together, we might have a chance.
Stop.
Just stop.
You devastated this
family when you walked out,
but we've been okay without you.
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids
anymore.
It's real this time.
I'm going for a walk.
I need some air.
I can appreciate that.
Our family is clearly gonna
need some counseling
in the future, but can we focus on
the fact that we're all about to die?
Right?
I mean...
I mean, Steph, didn't you say that Iris
knew someone that
cheated death or something?
Yeah, yeah, um...
In here, somewhere, it says...
that, uh, right here, J.B. found someone
who survived, but it
doesn't say anything about
who this J.B. was or...
Wait a minute.
I know that name.
My mom used to write me letters, and
she sometimes would talk about a friend of
hers named J.B. who worked at a
hospital.
Hospital?
Um, um, something, uh,
Something River Hospital.
Uh, Deep River.
Uh, Peace River Hospital.
Uh, Clear...
Hope...
Hope River?
That's it.
Shit, it's like an hour away.
I'm going.
I'm gonna go find him and talk to
him myself while I'm coming with you.
It's okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
Bobby, I...
What?
You need to stay here with your mom.
It's safer.
Yeah, fuck that.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not staying here by myself.
Well, it's too dangerous on the road for
you.
You can't...
No, I read Gammy's death book, okay?
All right?
I mean, there's, like, a
thousand house-related
deaths in that thing.
Man, you trip down the stairs, fall...
down a toilet or something.
I don't...
I don't know, but I'm not...
I'm not...
No way, I'm not staying here.
Hang on, hang on.
Hey, okay.
Okay, okay.
Too fast.
We'll go slow.
I'm gonna go open up the truck.
Charlie, check the back.
Got it.
Be careful.
The steps are slippery sometimes.
Oy!
Any of you fuckers do a nut check?
Excuse me?
You made cookies in that thing with peanut
butter in them just a few days ago.
This poor bastard so much as even touches
a nut, his throat is gonna close up
tight and...
You understand.
Where's the peanut butter?
Cabinet above the sink.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry, Bobby.
I just...
Hey, okay.
All clear.
Thank you.
You're a good brother, Eric.
Nut check.
What?
Let's go.
It was good.
I get it.
Let's go.
Come on.
It's only gonna get worse.
Damn it.
Wait.
I'm coming with you, bro.
Someone's gotta protect you.
Dad's calling again.
Tell him we just went for a ride
with Mom.
He's not gonna believe that.
At least it'll buy us some time.
Go ahead.
Death doesn't get us your dead will.
I always keep them where I can see
them.
I mean, you could've just had the real
thing, but it's okay.
Not everyone wants to be a mom.
Is that what you think?
That I didn't want to be your mom?
Look, I was raised by a woman who
taught me to see death everywhere.
I thought I could put it behind me,
but then when I had you and your
brother, all I could see were a hundred
different ways that you
and Charlie could die.
I didn't want you to leave the house.
I would freak out on you guys over
nothing.
One day, I looked at your face, and
I saw the same scared little girl that
I was growing up, and I knew that
if I stayed, I was gonna ruin your
life.
I have no idea if I did the
right thing.
But I'm here for you now.
It's okay.
I'm right behind you.
Hey, thanks, G-Buddy.
We got you.
The front desk is this way.
Oh.
Hi.
Um...
We're looking for J.B. And who are
you?
The front desk told us we could find
him down here.
Is that you?
That would be me.
William John Bloodworth.
But my friends call me J.B. I've
been waiting for you, Stephanie.
Charlie.
Darlene.
But no Howard.
No Julia.
So, which one of you is next?
I...
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
She was a special woman.
How did you know her?
She saved my life.
When?
At the Skyview.
My mother brought me with her to work
that night.
J.B., honey, I told you, you gotta
stay back there while I'm on stage.
I wasn't supposed to be there.
Except, of course, to die.
Stop playing!
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
The class is about to break!
Everyone needs to get off now!
Wait!
Iris!
You were the last to die.
You were the little boy.
Correct.
So all that time, she wasn't...
She wasn't just protecting our family.
She was protecting you, too.
Years later, she tracked me down.
Helped me see the truth.
We traded ideas.
I helped her fortify her cabin.
We became friends.
I even helped her get the best medical
care I could, considering her condition.
Iris said that you found
somebody who stopped
death and survived.
Yes.
And how do we do that?
There are only two ways.
By killing or by dying.
If you take a life, you get the
time that person had left.
What?
No.
I'm not gonna kill someone.
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
Then to truly break the cycle, you have
to die.
What does that mean?
A long time ago, a young woman named
Kimberly Corman found
herself on death's list, just
like you.
And when her turn finally came, she died.
Flatlined.
But her doctor managed to bring her back,
and that broke the chain.
All right, then.
We'll do that.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't Iris try that?
It's risky.
And if you fuck with death and lose,
things can get very messy.
Hang on, hang on.
Okay, wait.
No, there has to be another way.
Please, you have to help us.
For years, people have been coming to me
for advice.
Well, I'm tired.
I'm done with all that.
And now I'm sick just like Iris.
There's no running this time.
Fact is, you're all gonna die.
And after that, I will, too.
Now that my old friend is gone, I'm
retiring.
So what?
You're just gonna leave us here?
We need your help.
Where are you going?
I intend to enjoy the time I have
left.
And I suggest that you do the same.
Life is precious.
Enjoy every single second.
You never know when.
Good luck.
That's fantastic.
No.
No, that can't be it.
There has to be something here.
There has to be another answer.
Steph.
Steph, he gave us an answer.
Bobby's gotta die.
Eric!
Are you fucking insane?
We're not killing Bobby.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Am I the only guy that just listened
to that dude?
There's only one way.
We kill Bobby, we
resuscitate him, and then,
boom, you're all off death's list.
Congratulations.
There has to be something else, right?
I mean, there has to be another solution,
right, Steph?
No.
No, there's nothing else we can do, okay?
It's over.
We'll be done.
Stephen, listen to me.
You gotta trust me on this one, okay?
She's giving up on you.
I'm not going to.
Look, Iris found a way to hold death
off for decades.
So will we.
I trust that guy.
You trust that guy?
He was funny.
That just went there.
He was just oddly charismatic, and you know
that as well as I do.
Uh...
Eric and Bobby are gone.
Shit.
Shit!
I don't think I like this.
Hey, dude, we're in a hospital.
Remember?
There's doctors everywhere.
We kill you, they bring you back.
Everybody's safe.
We're heroes.
That is literally the
opposite of keeping me
safe.
What's the alternative, huh?
You want to kill someone and take the
time they have left?
How?
How would you even know how many years
they have?
No.
Well, I mean, no.
Of course not.
We would do that, right?
No, we would never.
Don't touch those babies.
Look, bottom line...
Flatlining's your best option.
What do you have to lose?
Okay, all right.
How would we even do that?
Well, see, I got an idea.
But it's a little nuts.
Your allergy is deadly, right?
Yeah.
Well...
Oh, hey, dude, wait.
No, look, all right?
If I'm going out, it's not gonna be
on those...
What is it?
Insulted bitches, all right?
Give me those.
Nice choice.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Come on.
Hey.
All right.
Come on.
You know, maybe this is a sign, so
we can just...
Ow.
Okay.
Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
I'm not giving up.
Can you help?
It's all right.
We work here.
Maintenance.
It's fine.
Put your headphones back on.
Dude, it's gonna fall.
It's gonna fall.
It's falling.
Get it out.
Hold it.
It's gonna fall.
Easy work.
Now what?
Come with me.
It's...
Hey, hang here.
I gotta get something.
What?
Don't move.
What are you talking about?
No, that's...
That's cool.
I searched the bathrooms.
They weren't in the RV?
No.
Look, if Eric was trying to kill Bobby,
where would they be?
I don't know, but there's a million ways
to die in a hospital.
Can I help you?
Excuse me?
No, uh, just came to see my Nana.
Hi, Gladys.
Here.
Lovely day today.
Got much time left?
I think so.
All metallic belongings and
devices that could interact
with the MRI's powerful magnet.
Hey, uh, dude, Charlie's trying to call.
I don't care about that.
Okay, come on.
Sit down.
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
What the hell?
No.
Sit in that.
I've got a great idea.
Okay.
There's an ER down the hall, so as
soon as you flatline, boom.
I'm gonna wheel your ass down, man.
They're gonna bring you right back.
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
Uh, it's right here.
Give it to me.
Why?
What is that?
Dude.
Give it.
Dude, listen.
The whole idea is that you have to
die.
Remember?
This keeps you alive.
Now sit.
Dude, we need to hurry.
Come on, go.
All right.
All right, eat up.
Hey, man.
The plan's great, but, you know, if it
doesn't work out...
It's going to work, Bobby.
Yeah.
Yeah, but, you know, just in case, and
I die for real...
Will you just, um...
Will you look after Paco?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I'll look after him.
Dude, I'm just saying.
I mean, the turtles live to be like
100 years old, and...
I'm not gonna take time for commitment.
Look at me.
Brother, I'm not gonna take care of Paco
because you are gonna be okay.
Me and you, we are going to fix
things for everyone right now.
I promise you, I'm not gonna let you
die.
Technically, I'm gonna
let you die, but then
I'm gonna bring you back.
Dude, it's not funny.
I'm just fucking with you.
Come on.
You got this.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's really good.
It's very good, I know.
So what, okay, other than good, what are
you feeling?
Nothing.
You gotta be kidding me.
What, you're telling me
you're not allergic anymore?
I don't know, man.
That's just perfect.
My hair grew out of it.
What grew out of it?
Fuck.
You know, I don't have a plan B
exactly.
Hey, you're doing it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're doing it.
Bobby, you're doing it.
Hey, I'm here with you.
I'm here with you.
Hey, hey, I can't give you that.
Hey.
Bobby, Bobby.
Please.
Bobby, this is all part of the plan.
Just calm down.
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
Try calling them again.
This is the only way we can do
this.
No!
Fuck!
Run!
Oh my God.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
No!
Why is Eric dead if he's not related
to Iris?
When you fuck with death, things get messy.
We have to get out of here.
It's not safe.
Then go where?
Nowhere is safe.
Except Iris' cabin.
She was able to survive there for decades.
And then she got her face blown off.
She only died because she left the cabin.
Outside is dangerous,
but inside is the safest
place that there is.
You're right.
It's the only place where we have any
advantage.
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin
forever?
Not you.
Me.
Mom, you can't leave.
We just got you back.
If anybody's gonna
live in that cabin, it's me.
And as long as I am alive,
death can't touch you.
- Mom.
- Let me do this.
He'll never let you get there on your own.
But I can see him coming.
We have to do this together.
Okay.
Let's go.
You should drive.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
Look at this place.
It's gonna be impossible
to get through that
gate.
He's about to make a move.
I don't know what it is.
We need to get you inside now.
Wait.
Wait, what?
Okay, let's get inside.
Shit.
What?
I can help.
Don't wait for me.
Just get inside.
Steph, if you get inside, I'll be safe.
Go.
Okay.
Come on.
Mom?
Mom!
Don't worry about me.
Go save your sister.
I'm gonna stay alive as long as-
Oh my god.
Are you okay?
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Charlie, what happened?
You're okay.
You died, and I brought you back.
You brought me back.
We're safe now.
Mom?
No.
She saved us.
Let's go home.
All right, I'm ready.
Well, there he is.
Wow.
Okay, Charlie.
All right, give us a spin.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
You look really good.
I have a great stylist.
Come on, we'll be late.
Where's Jenny?
I think she's still inside getting ready.
Here, let me fix this.
I'm really happy you could be here for
this.
Me too.
Oh.
You okay?
Yeah.
Can I have one cookie, please?
Charlie.
Look, it's sharp.
Thank you.
Steph, I want you to meet Jenny's dad,
Dr. Reddick.
Hey.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
We just adore Charlie.
And I understand he's quite the lifesaver.
Oh, yeah, you heard about that.
He, uh, brought me back from the dead.
Hmm?
Yeah.
What?
Well, technically, you weren't dead.
I mean, if you were unconscious and Charlie
got you breathing again,
then your heart didn't
stop.
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
So she wasn't dead?
Exactly.
She was lucky Charlie was there.
Yep, everything happens for a reason.
Jenny!
Sweetie, you look like a million bucks.
Oh my god, that was close.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh.